# José Gregorio Lezama González

# **Technical Lead & Web Developer**

@me@joseglego.io

% https://joseglego.io/



Vargas, Venezuela Remote & Willing to Relocate

Last Update: Jun 26, 2017

### **SUMMARY**

I am a **passionate developer** and a **coffee lover**.

As developer, I have experience in **back-end** and **front-end**. I am interested in learning new technologies, always following the best practices of each new language or framework. I enjoy front-end development, work with good eye for details and a good look and field & UX. Also, I really like to work back-end, too. I can work full-stack.

My last works were in: Front-End & UX, Back-End, Web Mobile, a little of Automation & Admin.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### <u>Cleteci</u>

Sep 2014 - Present

### Technical Lead <sup>2</sup> & Scrum Master <sup>1</sup>

1: Jan 2016 - Jan 2017; 2: Feb 2017 - Present

My tasks are: Revision of PR. Support team members in the development of new features. Support QA team fixing issues related to next release and production. Investigation related to new tools & technologies to be able to improve the quality of the environment, code and product. Define higher standards for code, product & documentation. Support thirds companies integrations. Define new features architectures. Do & Manage code refactoring (team between 4 and 9 devs).

### Web Developer

Sep 2014 - Dec 2015

My tasks were: Development of new features working on RESTful APIS & Web Applications.

### **Datos MEG**

Sep 2015 - Present

## Web Developer & Architect

We are working in a Web & Web Mobile Application with a RESTful API. I'm working as developer, admin of multiple servers & architect.

### **EDUCATION**

# Simón Bolívar University | Sep 2007 - Nov 2015

**Bachelor in Computer Engineering** 

**Internship:** Web System for <u>AtrioSeguros</u> Agents (Insurance Company) - **with Honors** 

**Specialization: 1.** Databases, **2.** Computer Graphics & **3.** Software Development Workshop: A Medical Emergencies Software for Centro Médico de Caracas, <u>iTriage</u> - <u>Current</u> Version.

**Electives:** 1. Mobile Development Tools, 2. Software Methodologies, 3. & 4. A.I. on Robotics and on Video Games, 5. Computer Graphics on Video Games & 6. Augmented Reality.

### **PROJECTS**

**Travel Contact**: RoR, AngularJS & Ionic

Latch: AngularJS

Phoebe: Django & jQuery

Atrio Seguros: AngularJS, ¡Query, Oracle & Java EE

Seguros Piramide: ¡Query & Oracle

**Datos MEG**: Django + DRF, Ionic & AngularJS

## **PERSONAL PROJECTS**

**Seller App**: AngularJS

**Attendance App**: AngularJS y angular-charts

## **TECHNOLOGIES & TOOLS** | Preferences on Bold

**Base:** OS X - Linux, Windows, Python, Javascript, Ruby, Java, C/C++, Bash, Haskell, Prolog.

**Web:** HTML, CSS, JS, jQuery, Bootstrap, Lodash, AngularJS, Gulp, Bower, Grunt, Django, Ruby on Rails.

**Tools:** Ionic/Phonegap, Emacs, PostgreSQL, SQLite3, git, Photoshop, Illustrator, Agile/Scrum

### **OTHER ACTIVITIES**

Daily English Lessons, about 3 hours per day. | Aug 2016

Urban Data Fest (<u>Venezuela</u>): 3rd Place, <u>Monitorea.la</u>: front-end developer (Angular) | Mar 2015

CodeSchool: Courses of JavaScript (10), Ruby (2), HTML/CSS (4) & others (3) | 2014 - Present

Professional FireFighter, Prehospital Care & Fire Science on C.B.V.U.S.B. Dept | May 2014 - March 2016

**Degree Project:** Selective Random, Level Test System Web & Military permissions (Django & JS)

3rd National Robotics Competition: Web platform development (Django & JS) | Apr 2013 - Sep 2013

IEEE Latin American Robotics Competition: Open<sup>1</sup> y SEK<sup>2</sup> | 1:Oct 2013, Arequipa - PE; 2:Oct 2012, Fortaleza - BR

Volunteer on Free Software International Conference Oct 2008, Malaga - ES

#### **LANGUAGES**

**Spanish** - Native speaker

**English** - Limited working proficiency